WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 4
There's no way he'll check online.
Not him.
Like he'd ever look up We Were Friends.
There's absolutely no way.
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
WE WERE FRIENDS
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 4
…YOON ONLY HAD EYES FOR TAE-HA…
Unbelievable. You little…
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 1
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 2
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 3
END OF EPISODE 3
CHAPTER 23: YOUR ROUGH THOUGHTS AND ANXIOUS LOOKS
EPISODE 7
You know what?
By the looks of things,
EBC is also excited
about the math class.
I don't blame them.
After all, it is taught by a math genius.
-Right? -Sure.
Of course, I totally respect your decision.
There's no pressure.
-No pressure at all. -No.
But sometimes, people do change their minds.
So, I thought I'd ask one last time.
In case you've changed…
I guess you haven't.
Do something, will you?
Today's the day.
Until we're are done with filming,
until EBC crew wraps up and leaves school,
I want everyone to stay sharp
and refrain from saying anything that could harm the school's reputation.
Homeroom teachers,
check your students' uniforms
and make sure they're on their best behavior.
Hopefully, everything will go off without a hitch.
Let's make sure this is a success.
We got this!
-Okay. -Of course.
Especially, our new teachers.
And the star of the show,
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
-Yes. -Thank you in advance.
Let's get this done!
Da-ju, everything's sorted, right?
Yes, by hook or by crook, we'll get what we need.
Aunt Young-hee.
Here's the man of the hour.
How is it that you look so good
in such flamboyant clothes?
Then, I'll put my faith in you.
-Yes, ma'am. -Good.
So, you're the principal's nephew.
Aunt Young-hee, clearly, the highlight of today's filming
will be my flute solo.
When the curtains open to reveal me on stage,
the spotlight will shine on me.
Basically, it'll be game over then.
Drink this.
What?
This is from my favorite place.
I know.
Drink up.
Keep drinking.
Go on, get every last drop.
You play so well.
I might have to quit teaching when the episode airs.
Did you see the new guys have all turned up in suits?
Honestly.
At best, they'll be caught in the background for a split second.
I actually feel sorry for them.
Tell me about it.
It's not kicking in right away.
Huh? What was that?
There's no time for this. I should go rehearse with the camera crew.
I'm sorry about this, E-den.
Film him on the sly?
Come on.
Don't put it like that. You make it sound illegal.
If you just happen to turn this on,
it will just happen to record whatever's in front of it.
I can't.
I really can't.
I need to keep my head down.
If I mess up again, I'll end up in jail.
Wait, sit back down.
I know Woo-su is a bit of a tyrant,
but he wouldn't send a student to jail.
You have to do this
to make up for all the time you goofed off in my class.
The gall of writing an essay in my class.
Do you know how hurt I was?
I'm really sorry about that, but…
There's a good reason why I'm entrusting this to you.
Don't you see that?
No.
If you don't do this,
we'll all be fired.
Are you okay with that?
Fired?
Principal's orders.
You know how she'll react
if we disobey her.
If we get fired,
I'll be fine.
But…
I'm not sure Mr. Jung and Mr. Yoon will land on their feet so easily.
Why not?
Mr. Jung will struggle to get another job because of his leg.
And as for Mr. Yoon, well…
That can't happen.
Exactly.
And besides,
I know everything.
About what?
Seriously?
I'm more observant than you think.
I could tell right away.
Did you really think I wouldn't notice?
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
I knew all along.
Right from the beginning.
Your rough thoughts
and anxious looks.
How could I not know?
I'll keep it a secret
as long as you film.
Okay?
How does he know about my novel?
Come on, kids. This isn't the time for idle chats.
Don't you know the camera crew is here today?
You girls should…
Don't forget you're the face of our school!
Kids, why aren't any of you studying?
Chat away in English.
Solve some math problems too. They're a delight, no?
Hey.
Hello?
Hey, kid.
Ji-a.
Where's your uniform?
I washed it.
Why?
Why wash it when you have to wear it to school?
I got oil on it.
You should have still worn it even if it had oil stains.
You should have worn it even if it was still soaking wet from the laundry.
Why today of all days?
Where's your gym clothes?
I don't have them with me.
Then borrow one and get changed.
Never mind.
That's not necessary. What's your name?
Choi Ji-a, ma'am.
Bring your desk and come with me.
Come on, don't dawdle.
There's no time.
What's going on?
Mr. Ga.
I'm going to take Choi Ji-a
and have her study in the counseling room until the fifth period.
-Bring your desk this way. -Go back to the classroom.
Mr. Ga.
Can I have a word?
As you know, we have the EBC crew here filming today.
She sleeps through class anyway,
and she isn't even wearing her uniform.
What's more, look at the state of her clothes.
Today is such an important day.
Given she might ruin the school's reputation,
it's better she's not here at all.
I'm terrified she'll end up on camera.
I still don't think it calls for hiding one of our students.
Don't be so naive, Mr. Ga.
TV shows are all scripted anyway.
Just until fifth period, okay?
Hey.
If you won't allow Ji-a to be here for the shoot,
then none of my class will take part in it.
Says who?
Mr. Ga.
I believe I made myself clear.
Let's go.
Pick it up.
Darn it.
I'll deal with you later, Mr. Ga.
Are they here?
I'm coming.
Go back inside. Everyone back to your seats.
CHAPTER 24: OUR SCHOOL RIGHT NOW
Why did you choose Murim Girls' High?
Our school…
I'm Kim Dan-ji, the Murim Girls' High connection.
The sports field is really nice. What else?
And we've got a really hot teacher.
-That's Mr. Yoon Dong-ju. -For real. No!
-No, Mr. Jung Gi-jeon-- -Mr. Yoon.
-Come on, Mr. Noh's the hot one. -No, that's Mr. Jung.
I don't think I can do it. Really.
Yes, you can!
There's nothing you can't do.
Don't be so negative.
Remember, all Murim students are full of potential.
-Go for it. -How is that relevant?
He's here.
I'm off. Don't mess up.
Got it?
Don't overthink this problem.
There are two solutions with the given conditions.
First, the value of x…
If he catches me filming him, he'll go ballistic.
And the tangent line…
On the other hand, he has told them about my novel
after telling me he'd keep it a secret.
Let's just do it.
Mr. Ga.
I…
have a question.
What is it?
Well, I heard
a famous university in another country
offered you a job as a professor.
Why did you come here instead?
Why are you asking that now?
I've been curious all along.
It's amazing to have a genius like you teaching at our school.
I thought there might be a special reason.
Isn't a question like that better saved for after class?
Mr. Ga, we're all curious.
-Tell us. -If you tell us, we'll study harder.
-Tell us! -Tell us!
-Tell us! -Quiet, everyone.
Fine.
I guess it might be helpful in thinking about your own futures.
The six kids invited to the Mathematical Olympiad
attend two separate training camps.
On the day of the first camp,
as soon as we finished registering, our first exam was waiting for us.
That exam…
Take it out.
I said take it out.
Mr. Ga! Just a moment. Let me explain.
Mr. Noh told me if I didn't do it,
you'd all get fired.
That's the only reason I did it, sir.
Please hear me out, sir.
We can't have you all lose your jobs, can we, sir?
Noh Da-ju.
You asked a student to film me behind my back?
Have you lost it?
Mr. Ga, why don't you calm down
so we can talk about it?
What do you mean by filming behind your back?
Who would…
do something so unethical?
How could you film me like this?
You of all people should know better.
Guys.
What's going on?
Hey.
That was so long ago.
You have to move on.
You can't go on like this.
Hey!
Mr. Ga.
May I have a word?
Sir.
-Jeez, you idiot. -What's the matter?
Did something happen to Mr. Ga in the past?
I don't know the details.
But when Woo-su was about ten,
someone started stalking him after he was on TV as a math prodigy.
I heard that crazy stalker
would turn up at his school and his house
to film and take photos of him behind his back.
Eventually,
he even kidnapped him.
Kidnapped?
That left Woo-su traumatized.
My goodness.
What's wrong?
Mr. Ga.
This is the real world.
You might be smart,
but being obedient
will help you get further in life.
It won't kill you to get filmed,
so what's the big deal?
Please excuse me.
If you're not going to cooperate,
you leave me no choice.
SUSPENSION NOTICE
YOON DONG-JU
The rest of you might land on your feet,
but if Mr. Yoon loses his job here, he'll struggle.
From this equation,
it's clear that negative four is the average rate of change.
Next, we have to calculate f prime of x.
Two x minus three.
What was the average rate of change again?
-Negative four. -Negative four.
It was negative four.
He could have just filmed from the start. Why all the drama?
Tell me about it.
We're going to end up finishing late because of him.
-I'm so annoyed. -So the value of x
is negative one-half,
which happens to be a number between negative three and two.
Accordingly, c is…
It's finally over.
CHAPTER 25: I ONLY FEEL BETRAYED BECAUSE I TRUSTED YOU
Aunt Young-hee.
Wait, what am I doing here?
You said you were going to take a nap because you didn't sleep well last night,
and you've been asleep all this time.
Did I?
That doesn't make sense.
What about the filming?
It's all over.
What?
No way.
No.
No. Don't go. Stop.
I can't believe this!
Don't go!
No!
You're not a snake charmer!
Sir…
Mr. Ga.
I…
I'm so sorry.
I would never have filmed you if I had known what had happened to you.
No.
I shouldn't have filmed you regardless.
I'm really sorry. I made a mistake.
You asked me a question in math class.
Do you know what flashed through my head at that exact moment?
"Is she actually starting to like math now?"
When I heard your question, I went, "All right."
"It's a tangent, but it's a start."
I figured my story
might get you interested in math,
so I was going to give you a sincere answer.
But you…
I guess I only feel betrayed
because I trusted you.
Forget it. Just go.
I apologize for
disappointing you.
Just go.
Get up.
I said get up. Enough with the acting.
Eui-ju.
Hey, Eui-ju.
Wake up, Eui-ju!
Eui-ju.
Stay with me, Eui-ju!
Subtitle: Paul Carver